Father,
does Mother's death
have anything to do with you?
I can explain.
Listen to me.
I did it for
Kuizhou City.
For...
For the people.
Ultimately, you did it for yourself.
Go explain it
to Mother.
Madam. Madam,
would you like to take this beauty fan?
Go greet them.
Madam,
please come in.
would you like to take this beauty fan?
Madam.
This is personally blended by our Pavilion Master
using magnolia juice.
I'm here
to get my makeup done.
I want the 'Natural Elegance' look.
Go.
You have great taste, Madam.
Are you attending a banquet or...
I'm going to
Jinxiuxuan for a job interview
to be a clothes envoy.
Their new Yanluo yarn
suits a slender figure best.
The Pavilion Master often says 'Natural Elegance'
means to have one's own natural beauty.
A woman's beauty
should be like the flowers and plants of the four seasons,
spring orchids and autumn chrysanthemums,
each with its own merits.
A healthy body is the most beautiful.
You just need to show
your truest self.
I believe
the boss will see it.
Thank you for your guidance, Pavilion Master.
Thanks for storing them.
Pavilion Master.
Your kindness is like a second life to me.
How could it be hard work?
If you hadn't reached out,
I'd still be struggling in that quagmire.
You were willing to reach out from the quagmire,
so you could catch my hand.
Moreover,
I found your bookkeeping skills
are even better than your makeup skills.
I'm just making the best use of your talents.
Pavilion Master.
No need to bow.
Just keep up the good work with the accounts.
Yes.
Teach them well.
I will do my best
to live up to your trust.
You have something on your mind, Pavilion Master.
Now that Yanzhi Pavilion is exclusively for the royal family,
and you are all here on weekdays,
our foundation is solid.
I want
to open a branch in Nanzhou.
Pavilion Master,
is there someone you can't let go of?
Even if I can't let go,
he is already the Lord of Kuizhou.
Having taken on this heavy responsibility,
he has his own things to accomplish.
And I
also have things to accomplish.
Back then,
I told you, Lady Fang,
never to touch that poisonous rouge again.
Now,
the toxins have spread from your heart
to your whole body.
How much time do I have left?
At most,
one month.
You didn't even say a word
before leaving.
Haven't you been
training troops these days?
Running back here and leaving General Cheng and the others behind,
aren't you afraid they'll tear down the racecourse?
These past few days,
they haven't been discussing the defense.
They've been discussing my marriage.
Chu Shengyi.
I have feelings for you.
It really feels much better to say it out loud.
Don't say anything yet.
Let me finish.
I don't know when it started,
but that doesn't matter.
I just wanted you to know.
We
both have our own paths to take.
Then let's
say goodbye here.
This is...
A parting gift.
These carrier pigeons
were trained by me personally.
They remember the way back to Kuizhou.
Okay.
Be careful on the road.
In the future...
I
had warned Madam Fang before.
She must never again
use that poisonous rouge.
If she
insists on using it,
in less than a month,
her life will wither away.
Not long after,
bad news came from Quentan.
The Khan died suddenly,
and the young prince Yelu Hula succeeded him.
The flames of war reignited,
and war drums beat again on the Kuizhou and Quentan border.
This battle
lasted for a full three years.
After years of bitter fighting,
Chu Shengyi finally defeated Quentan
at Kuishui yesterday.
Where have you been all these years?
I thought you were already...
Originally,
I wanted to find a beautiful place to wait for death.
Perhaps I wasn't meant to die,
I met a wandering doctor.
It took three years
to completely clear the poison from the rouge.
This must still be a dream,
right?
This is not a dream, right?
This is not a dream.
I really missed you.
Why are you here?
Earlier this year,
I gradually opened branches
of Yanzhi Pavilion in Nanzhou.
It's close to Quentan,
so trade is inevitable.
Hearing that you were trapped,
I had someone
add something special
to the goods sent to Quentan.
The fire last night,
was it to your liking?
Thank you, my wife,
for relieving my army.
The Lord of Kuizhou
never marrying,
is that okay?
I already have a wife.
The divorce letter is still with me.
Then I will
propose again.
Hold a wedding for you,
a wedding that belongs to Fang Zhuozhuo
and Chu Shengyi.
No.
Why?
This time,
let me propose.
I've already given you the betrothal gifts.